Isaac Rutledge-Wilson

Tacoma, WA 98406 opledople5644@gmail.com 253.2405243

ISAAC RUTI FDGF-WII SON

Seeking a position that where a strong sense of responsibility, problem solving with the ability to learn quickly and excellent communication skills will be assets. I am currently studying for the Comptia A+ exam. I have over 8 years of excellent customer service and problem solving.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Warehouse Unloader

Westrock - Tacoma, WA October 2019 to Present

Fork lift driving
Production
Heavy lifting
Walking frequently
Warehouse• Labor and fork lift

Wireless Sales Consultant

verizon - Bremerton, WA April 2019 to September 2019

Retail sales associate. Sell phones and other gadgets and accessories. Cash register. Customer service.

Customer Service

U-haul - Auburn, WA July 2016 to September 2018

FMT (Facility Maintenance Tech)

- Landscaping
- Painting
- Pressure Washing

Customer Service Rep

U-haul - Lakewood, WA March 2010 to July 2016

Customer support both on phone and in person. issue escalation.

Unit Supply Clerk

United States Army National Guard October 2010 to February 2011 Unit Supply. Responsibilities: Supplied the unit with gear, weapons, and uniforms and managed stock. Kept records and verified their accuracy with matching stock.

Education

GED

Tacoma community College

September 2011

Skills

- Customer Care
- Customer Service
- Customer Support
- CSR
- · Computer Skills
- Sales
- training
- Merchandising
- Retail
- General Labor
- General Laborer
- Construction Laborer
- Forklift
- Factory
- Warehouse Associate
- Warehouse Experience
- Construction
- Shipping & Receiving (3 years)
- Warehouse Management (2 years)
- Microsoft Word (10+ years)
- Administrative Experience (3 years)
- Order Picking
- Landscape Maintenance
- Heavy Lifting
- Handyman
- Freight Experience
- Facilities Maintenance
- Driving Experience
- Drivers license (7 years)
- Operating Systems (6 years)

- Typing (7 years)
- Logistics
- HTML5 (1 year)
- CSS3 (1 year)
- · Load & Unload
- Pallet Jack
- JavaScript
- Git
- Technical support
- E-commerce
- Help desk
- · Software troubleshooting
- · Computer networking
- Windows
- Linux

Certifications and Licenses

Drivers License

Assessments

Basic computer skills: PC — Proficient

December 2020

Performing basic computer operations, navigating a Windows OS, and troubleshooting common computer problems.

Full results: Proficient

Customer focus & orientation — Highly Proficient

December 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.